# PRANJAL JAIN

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Work under the dome of renowned and well esteemed firm like yours enabling me to study the design process more closely and also bring an engineering perspective and creative problem-solving approach to create products and experiences people love to use.

#### **EDUCATION**

2020 (expected)	THE LNMIIT  B. Tech (CSE)
2016	India International School, Jaipur Class 12 (CBSE) Percentage: 88.4%
2014	India International School, Jaipur Class 10 (CBSE) CGPA: 9.6

#### SKILLS

SOFTWARE Photoshop, Illustrator, XD,

After Effects, Premier, Balsamiq, Figma, Invision

**DESIGN** Design Research, User Interface,

Web Design, Interaction Design, Prototyping, Wireframing, Personas, User Flows

**DEVELOPMENT** HTML/CSS

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **UX DESIGN INTERN**

May 2019 - present

LUCIDEUS

I worked on 3 projects wherein I was responsible for **reseaching on the B2B security trends** and hence charting the User flow for the AI and ML backed platform for realtime Enterprise security analysis, **developing wireframes** followed by designing fully intreactive prototype for the MVP facilitating the company to grab a few-mllion dollars deal

#### **UX DESIGNER**

Nov 2018 - May 2019

ELROUTE

My work spans from wireframing and helping with research studies to creating visuals for onboarding animations and UI, as well as animating and prototyping responsive screens for the B2B platform.

#### **CREATIVE ASSOCIATE**

June 2018 - July 2018

UPSIDE STORY

Worked on several designing projects that included designing infographics, web designs, package designs, design mock-ups, logo branding, social media creatives, for various Jaipur based clients.

## WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Dec 2017 - Jan 2018

GIRNAR SOFT

Created Web Application shopping cart using spring MVC. Shopping card includes feature such as add a cart, remove cart item and update quantity of cart item.

## **KEY PROJECTS**

## SAFE ASSURE DASHBOARD / LUCIDEUS

Designed an AI and ML backed platform to quantify, measure and mitigate enterprise wide cyber risks in real time demonstrating chronological user profile interfaces with in-deth analysis over geographical, channel lines and agent classes through extensive design process.

## **DESIGN CASE STUDY**

Designed a fully automated mobile application as a design case study for the fictitious company whose sole purpose is to feed the 12% of population who order food everyday and end up with a mediocre option, even after wasting a major amount of time ordering food online; delivering user personnas, workflow diagrams, lo-fi Wireframes, Hi-fi Prototype.

## WHATSAPP MESSENGER RE-DESIGN CASE STUDY

Redesigned Whatsapp elements keeping the existing modules in place to provide better engagement and easy interactions enhancing overall interactions and making it easier, attractive and clean by introducing visually aesthetic elements.

# **EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

## NATIONAL LEVEL PAINTING COMPETITION

Was one of the finalist at the competition organised by Canadian High Commision

## **CBSE TABLE TENNIS CLUSTERS**

Leaded my school team as Team Captain and made it to Top6 twice.

POETRY RECITALS
BLOGGING
FREELANCE DESIGNER

# POSITION OF RESPONSIBILTY

## CAMPUS AMBASSADOR / VIACOM 18

2018- present

Responsible for coordinating various events undertaken by Viacom 18 in the city.

## SUB-COORDINATOR / RAZZMATAZZ

2017

Overlooked the organisation and preparation of the event in Vivacity'18.

# HOUSE CAPTAIN

2015-2016

Steered student of the house ensuring high levels of participation from all and oversee the management of the teams bagging the Sports Trophy